<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_full_name">Battery Indicator Pro</string>
    <string name="app_name">Battery Indicator</string>
    <string name="settings_activity_name">Battery Indicator Settings</string>
    <string name="info_activity_name">About Battery Indicator</string>
    <string name="log_view_activity_name">Battery Indicator Logs</string>

    <string name="degree_symbol">°</string>
    <string name="fahrenheit">Fahrenheit</string>
    <string name="celsius">Celsius</string>

    <string name="discharging_from">Discharging from</string>
    <string name="charging_from">Charging from</string>
    <string name="fully_charged">Fully Charged</string>

    <string name="one_six_needed">Sorry, Android 1.6+ needed!</string>

    <string name="currently_using">Currently using</string>
    <string name="currently_set_to">Currently set to:</string>
    <string name="currently_disabled">Currently Disabled</string>

    <string name="info"><b>Intro</b>
      \nThis is <i>Battery Indicator Pro</i>, the \"pro\"
      version of the popular free app, <i>Battery Indicator</i>.
      It\'s available from the Android Market for US$0.99, but it\'s
      an open source project, which means you can download the source
      for free
      from <a href="http://www.darshancomputing.com/android/battery_indicator/">the
	project website</a>.\n

      \n<b>Summary</b>
      \n<i>Battery Indicator</i> is a small, simple application
      for the Android mobile operating system. It\'s simply a little icon
      that lives in the status bar and shows you the percentage of battery
      charge left.\n

      \n<b>Limitations</b>
      \n(<i>These are out of my control.</i>)
      \n• The app can only display what the phone tells it. Most phones report
      every 1%, but a few (notably the Motorola Droid) only report every
      10%.
      \n• There\'s no way to remove the built-in battery icon.\n

      \n<b>Features</b>
      \n• Small, simple, and easy to read.
      \n• It doesn\'t do any polling. It receives a broadcast message from the OS
      when the battery status changes, then it simply updates the icon and
      goes back to sleep. What this means is that it will take up a small
      amount of RAM, but essentially 0 CPU cycles, so it can\'t drain your
      battery.
      \n• Automatically starts when the phone boots up if it was running when the
      phone shut down.\n

      \n<b>Pro-only Features</b>
      \n• High-resolution images (on devices that support them).
      \n• Easy access to Battery Use screen (requires Android 1.6+).
      \n• Configure to use Fahrenheit or Celsius as the battery temperature unit.
      \n• Configure to always start on boot, never start on boot, or start on boot
      if the app was running on shutdown.
      \n• Configure the icon to turn red below a configurable threshold and/or turn
      green above a configurable threshold.
      \n• The satisfaction of supporting the developer.\n

      \n<b>No Warranty</b>
      \nThis software is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
      WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
      MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.\n
      \nWhile I do my best to make sure that it works well and does not
      cause problems, I am not responsible for any damage or inconvenience
      it may cause under any circumstance.\n

      \n<b>Acknowledgments</b>
      \nMany thanks are due to Google and all of the open-source coders who made
      the Android platform and this app possible.\n

      \n<b>Translations</b>
      \nI need help translating this app to other languages.  If you would like to
      help, please send me an email.\n

      \n<b>Contact</b>
      \nIf you have questions, comments, problems, or feedback of any other sort,
      please email me at <a href="mailto:android@darshancomputing.com">android@darshancomputing.com</a>.
</string>
</resources>
