<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_full_name">Battery Indicator Pro</string>
  <string name="app_name">Battery Indicator</string>
  <string name="settings_activity_name">Battery Indicator Settings</string>
  <string name="settings_help_activity_name">Battery Indicator Settings Help</string>
  <string name="info_activity_name">About Battery Indicator</string>
  <string name="log_view_activity_name">Battery Indicator Logs</string>

  <string name="menu_help">Help</string>

  <string name="degree_symbol">°</string>
  <string name="fahrenheit">Fahrenheit</string>
  <string name="celsius">Celsius</string>

  <string name="discharging_from">Discharging from</string>
  <string name="charging_from">Charging from</string>
  <string name="fully_charged">Fully Charged</string>

  <string name="one_six_needed">Sorry, Android 1.6+ needed!</string>

  <string name="currently_using">Currently using</string>
  <string name="currently_set_to">Currently set to:</string>
  <string name="currently_disabled">Currently Disabled</string>

  <string name="info"><b>Intro</b>
    \nThis is <i>Battery Indicator Pro</i>, the \"pro\"
    version of the popular free app, <i>Battery Indicator</i>.
    It\'s available from the Android Market for US$0.99, but it\'s
    an open source project, which means you can download the source
    for free
    from <a href="http://www.darshancomputing.com/android/battery_indicator/">the
      project website</a>.\n

    \n<b>Summary</b>
    \n<i>Battery Indicator</i> is a small, simple application
    for the Android mobile operating system. It\'s simply a little icon
    that lives in the status bar and shows you the percentage of battery
    charge left.\n

    \n<b>Limitations</b>
    \n(<i>These are out of my control.</i>)
    \n• The app can only display what the phone tells it. Most phones report
    every 1%, but a few (notably the Motorola Droid) only report every
    10%.
    \n• There\'s no way to remove the built-in battery icon.\n

    \n<b>Features</b>
    \n• Small, simple, and easy to read.
    \n• It doesn\'t do any polling. It receives a broadcast message from the OS
    when the battery status changes, then it simply updates the icon and
    goes back to sleep. What this means is that it will take up a small
    amount of RAM, but essentially 0 CPU cycles, so it can\'t drain your
    battery.
    \n• Automatically starts when the phone boots up if it was running when the
    phone shut down.\n

    \n<b>Pro-only Features</b>
    \n• High-resolution images (on devices that support them).
    \n• Easy access to Battery Use screen (requires Android 1.6+).
    \n• Configure to use Fahrenheit or Celsius as the battery temperature unit.
    \n• Configure to always start on boot, never start on boot, or start on boot
    if the app was running on shutdown.
    \n• Configure the icon to turn red below a configurable threshold and/or turn
    green above a configurable threshold.
    \n• The satisfaction of supporting the developer.\n

    \n<b>No Warranty</b>
    \nThis software is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
    WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.\n
    \nWhile I do my best to make sure that it works well and does not
    cause problems, I am not responsible for any damage or inconvenience
    it may cause under any circumstance.\n

    \n<b>Acknowledgments</b>
    \nMany thanks are due to Google and all of the open-source coders who made
    the Android platform and this app possible.\n

    \n<b>Translations</b>
    \nI need help translating this app to other languages.  If you would like to
    help, please send me an email.\n

    \n<b>Contact</b>
    \nIf you have questions, comments, problems, or feedback of any other sort,
    please email me at <a href="mailto:android@darshancomputing.com">android@darshancomputing.com</a>.
  </string>

  <string name="pref_cat_logging">Logging</string>
  <string name="pref_enable_logging">Enable Logging</string>
  <string name="pref_enable_logging_summary">Log battery state changes?</string>
  <string name="pref_enable_logging_help">
    If enabled, Battery Indicator will log battery state changes
    (e.g., the phone is unplugged or becomes fully charged).
  </string>
  <string name="pref_view_logs">View Logs...</string>
  <string name="pref_view_logs_help">
    This isn't a setting; just select (press) this to access the logs
    that have been collected.
  </string>

  <string name="pref_cat_keyguard">Lock Screen / Keyguard</string>
  <string name="pref_cat_keyguard_help">
    Android allows apps to disable and reenable what it calls the
    "keyguard", which you probably think of as the lock sreen.  Beyond
    simply disabling and reenabling it, however, there is no more
    control — I can't control which keys turn the screen on, for
    example.
  </string>
  <string name="pref_confirm_manual_disable">Confirm Manual Disable</string>
  <string name="pref_confirm_manual_disable_summary">Confirm when manually disabling lock screen?</string>
  <string name="pref_confirm_manual_disable_help">
    If checked, a confirmation dialog will pop up when you try to
    manually disable the lock screen.  This is primarily intended to
    prevent new users from accidentally disabling their lock screen
    without knowing it.  If you disable the lock screen with any
    regularity, you'll probably want to turn this off.
  </string>
  <string name="pref_auto_disable">Auto-disable Lock Screen</string>
  <string name="pref_auto_disable_summary">Disable the lock screen when charging?</string>
  <string name="pref_auto_disable_help">
    If checked, then whenever the device is plugged in, Battery
    Indicator with disable the lock screen, and whenever the device is
    unplugged, it will enable it again.
  </string>

  <string name="pref_cat_temperature_unit">Temperature Unit</string>
  <string name="pref_convert_to_fahrenheit">Convert to Fahrenheit</string>
  <string name="pref_convert_to_fahrenheit_help">
    Android reports the battery temperature in degrees Celsius.  If
    you prefer to see the battery temperature in degrees Fahrenheit,
    check this option, and the app will convert for you.
  </string>

  <string name="pref_cat_autostart">Autostart</string>
  <string name="pref_autostart_at_boot">Autostart at Boot</string>
  <string name="pref_autostart_at_boot_summary">Start Battery Indicator When Device Boots?</string>
  <string name="pref_autostart_at_boot_help">
    Controls whether Battery Indicator should start itself
    automatically when the device boots up.\n\nThe "If Running on
    Shutdown" option works with regard to whether you've most recently
    manually started or stopped Battery Indicator.  So if you kill
    Battery Indicator through some other means, like a task killer,
    then Battery Indicator doesn't know you stopped it, and it will
    still start at boot up if you have it set to this.
  </string>

  <string name="pref_cat_status_duration">Status Duration (For/Since...)</string>
  <string name="pref_status_dur_est">When to Estimate Hours</string>
  <string name="pref_status_dur_est_summary">Stop Showing Time and Start Estimating Hours</string>
  <string name="pref_status_dur_est_help">
    Determines when the notification switches from saying, e.g.,
    "Unplugged Since 1:10 PM" to saying something like "Unplugged for
    1 Hour".  The first way is more accurate, because it tells you
    exactly (to the minute) when the status changed, but many people
    prefer the simpler to comprehend estimate of the number of elapsed
    hours, so they make that happen sooner than the default of 12
    hours.
  </string>

  <string name="pref_cat_color">Color</string>
  <string name="pref_color_preview">Color Preview</string>
  <string name="pref_red">Use Red Icon</string>
  <string name="pref_red_summary">Use red icon when charge is low?</string>
  <string name="pref_red_thresh">Red Threshold</string>
  <string name="pref_red_thresh_summary">Red Icon Below What Charge Percentage?</string>
  <string name="pref_amber">Use Amber Icon</string>
  <string name="pref_amber_summary">Use amber icon when charge is medium?</string>
  <string name="pref_amber_thresh">Amber Threshold</string>
  <string name="pref_amber_thresh_summary">Amber Icon Below What Charge Percentage?</string>
  <string name="pref_green">Use Green Icon</string>
  <string name="pref_green_summary">Use green icon when charge is high?</string>
  <string name="pref_green_thresh">Green Threshold</string>
  <string name="pref_green_thresh_summary">Green Icon At or Above What Charge Percentage?</string>
</resources>
